# **Hyuk Jin Kwon**

Address: 356 Havendale Crescent, Waterloo, Ontario, Canada

**Tel:** (548) 255-0872

E-mail: wkwkdaus79@gmail.com

Portfolio: https://hyukjin87.github.io/Portfolio/

Linkedin: https://www.linkedin.com/in/hyuk-jin-kwon-82a040231/

Github: <a href="https://github.com/hyukjin87/">https://github.com/hyukjin87/</a>

## **OBJECTIVE:**

Highly accomplished game designer with a successful track record in the Korean gaming industry, including 7 years of experience at Netmarble N2 and Entwell. Skilled in navigating the fast-paced mobile market, adapting to trends, and collaborating effectively across teams. Seeking new opportunities in a larger market after relocating to Canada with a family and acquiring a diploma in Software Engineering from Conestoga College. Quick learner with meticulous attention to detail.

#### **EMPLOYMENT HISTORY:**

Chef AUG 2022 - Present

Ah-so Fine Food Inc - Kitchener, Canada

Game Developer MAR 2017 – DEC 2021

Netmarble N2 - Seoul, South Korea

Game System Designer JUN 2015 – MAR 2017

Entwell - Seoul, South Korea

#### **EDUCATION:**

Conestoga College – Waterloo, Canada SEP 2021 – APR 2023

Diploma in Software Engineering Technician GPA: 3.41

Yeonsung University – Gyeonggi-do, South Korea FEB 2008 – FEB 2012

Associate degree in Information Communication Technology GPA: 3.92

## SKILLS:

- ✓ Programming Languages: C, C++, C#, .NET and WPF, Python, JavaScript, mySQL, ASP, PHP
- ✓ Software: Proficient in Microsoft Word and Excel, Unity
- ✓ Languages: English and Korean
- ✓ Certification: Computer Specialist in Spreadsheet & Database Level
- ✓ Game design and planning, Event management and data analysis
- ✓ Collaborative teamwork, Adaptability in a fast-paced mobile market